Look, isn't it amazing? Emo emo.
So cute! Eggplant. That's funny.
It's an eggplant.
So, look at that.
Ta-da! The first anniversary of Chewate's anniversary book!
This one is a little bit in my possession right now
and I'd like to take a look at this emo one time.
Look, there are some photogravures from those days...
There it is!
There he is!
Can I see this page?
With Gyonchan! It's the three of us!
That's Team 4! That's right! We're all on Team 4 now.
I'm captain now!
Look at all these interesting personalities in the West Japan Fours.
Wait a minute, that's funny!
They're as unique as ever!
Wow, there's not enough tape on the pillars behind the theater.
There's only 9 tapes, which is probably more than AKB has ever had in its history.
It's ready for those who know what they're talking about.
Oh, no! It's out!
It's out!
This is the most important one!
It's so cute!
Oh, my God, that's just so emo.
Oh, I'm done. I'm done with the pictures.
Oh, yeah! And what I want to do today is, no more emo blocks.
I want each person to put up some kind of photo, like a profile.
And since this is the first anniversary of the book, they're going to introduce you with a questionnaire, like an introduction.
I'll put Nagi-chan's page in the middle of the page. That's it! Like this.
There is also a NARTA version. Do you remember how you answered this questionnaire?
Do you remember what you answered? Today, I want to ask you, "Do you remember what you answered? I definitely don't remember!
Yes, I saw this on TV, and I was wondering if you remember what you said in your old questionnaire.
I saw this project and thought I would like to do it with NARTA, so I ordered this anniversary book from my parents' house.
Nice! Thank you, Mom!
Thank you very much! I'd like to do a little bit of it!
Nartao! Now, you probably saw Nagi-chan's page earlier, but there is a kind of a confession.
First of all, the balloon. Yes, that's right. I think this one is pretty easy. I think this one is pretty easy.
I think she might be using a dialect, so sure. I'll think about confessing once? Of the blurb.
But really, by the way, I don't really remember, so I think it's like this. I'm sure. Maybe it's a dialect. Okay.
I'm going to move on.
I'll show you. Se-no!
Then!
Taikyasukichan, buchisukichan!
Oh! How are they?
They're both buu.
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
I used to say this a lot.
I used to say "Taiyasuki-chan" a lot too.
No way! Hey!
I have an image of Buchi saying it a lot too.
We said it to each other.
What'll it be then?
Next.
Special skills.
If you guessed one again, would you be OK?
Do you remember how many you wrote down?
I think I can guess.
You only have one?
Two, two.
Definitely two.
Then I'll write them down.
You did it.
I'm sure I can do it next time.
No, I'm confident, too.
I think I can do it.
I think so.
Okay, let's go.
Ready!
Ta-da!
I'm kendama unicyclist.
Dance Okoto and Shuji.
Okay, well, I'm Japan.
Oh! Yay!
Pros.
What? Pros?
Strengths. What are my strengths?
What did you write?
One year. That was you in your first year, right?
That would have been my first year.
But I might have had this.
Let's go!
I hate to lose!
My pace.
Same as now.
I'm still saying I'll do my best at my own pace.
Yes, yes, yes.
Phone call.
I'm sure it will be.
Oh! Bing bong!
Yes!Yes!
Was it me?
Wrong.
Think positive.
Wow.
But you're right, yesterday too. I was positive thinking.
You were thinking. I'm still thinking. But it's still the same.
Narjeh comes with another word,
I'm a high orrier and I hate to lose.
Ha-ha-ha-ha. Strong.
Wait, wait. Strong.
I mean, the atmosphere then and now are totally different.
On the contrary, I feel like I have an air of being competitive now. In my mind.
I don't think you could tell from the feeling I had back then, but it was a feeling like, "I hate to lose. I was like, "I hate to lose," or something like that.
That's probably why I wrote "I look like this," but I like it better when I go to the trouble of writing "I look like this.
Ha-ha-ha. It's funny.
NARUTAO channel.
2.
Charm points then.
Charm point? I feel like I change this every year.
It's the first year, right?
Here we go. Ready?
There you go. A mole on the cheek.
Oh, he looks like he's about to say something. Bangs.
Bangs?
What do you think?
It's a boo with no one.
Ehhhh!
I know. It's probably the eyes, right?
Eyes, huh?
I think it's eyes.
Bing bong.
It was an eye.
I got lost with the eyes.
Outline.
Oh, wait.
Eh, wait.
Contour!
Contour, indeed.
I wonder if that's the point.
I think I drew it sometime ago.
Oh, really?
He said he was praised for his outline.
Oh, yes. Yes, that's right.
Of course.
I definitely drew the moles on my cheeks on some last-minute train.
I definitely drew it. That was the last part.
I think that's how I do it.
Wait, wait, wait. I can't say either.
I don't know. Wait, wait.
Teeth!
How is it?
Aaaaah!
I wonder what it is.
Oh, wait. The more you say it, the better I feel.
I wonder.
Ehhhh. I wonder where it is.
What should I say?
Ah, eh, are you saying "dance" here?
Yeah, I'm not.
Ah, it's not like that.
I don't know.
It's not that bad.
But it's a point of attraction, isn't it?
Well, yes.
It's like a part, isn't it?
It's not a part.
Stage.
It's okay, it's a style.
It might say boobs.
Oh, come on.
It says "tits" at my age.
I'm sorry.
I'm very stylish.
I don't need this scale.
You don't need it.
Then, please answer the question.
Mature looking.
Oh, I see.
Favorite word.
Favorite word?
Wow.
I wonder.
Okay, here we go. Ready.
If you do it, it will be done. Anything that must be done, will be done.
Be a genius at hard work.
Ah, I did it!
Akane & Yuuka, I remember this. What happened? You are geniuses of effort. It's a nice line.Akane & Yuuka, I remember this. What happened? You're a genius for hard work. It's a nice line, though.
Yuuka, you've written it somewhere. Probably.
Akane I've written this somewhere too, but not in the first year.
Yuuka The one from the first year is attached to my head: "I can manage.
Akane Oh, I can manage! I used to wear a T-shirt that said "I can manage," for a while. That's part of it.
Akane So, no. I thought you looked up a lot of words with "naru" in them.
Yuka Ah, I see. So, I can manage.
Akane: Nasseba naru. I don't know if "nasseba" means this.
Naru is this? So "Naseba" is this one.
Well, yes, I looked this one up too, at that time.
I was like, "I have no choice but to do it," so I said, "This is the word.
I even remember the background.
Yuka Wow!
Akane I did remember it unexpectedly.
Yuka I was thinking about this, but he said this a lot, too. It's a word that was said to me.
Akane I thought it was a nice word, but what did you say at that time?
Akane What did you say?
Yuka I'm happy.
Akane, you said it! You said it! I know!
You said "happily ever after", didn't you?
Akane, you were saying it! She was trying to get in.
Yuka, the fashion award?
Akane, I was aiming for the fashion award.
I was aiming for it. It's a dialect of Yamaguchi Prefecture, too.
Yuuka Oh, I see.
Akane There is a region where people say "Happiness, please" which means "Thank you" and "May your happiness come to you".
Akane I definitely remember that the lower part of the country often says "happily-masu".
Yuka I was about to enter.
Akane That's interesting. You were trying to enter.
Yuka Next. Favorite food.
Akane, your favorite food.
Yuka Eh!
Akane, this is the hardest one.
Akane That's true.
Yuuka I don't understand the most.
Akane, what did I say I liked? I also had quite a few booms.
Yuuka It changes, doesn't it?
Akane Yes, I remember the second year was melon bread.
Akane, wait, wasn't that the first year? Maybe.
Yuuka, did you come?
Akane, ready! Then!
Akane, popcorn, Taipien, something sweet.
Yuuka, I have a feeling it's something like this.
Akane, chicken wings, onions.
Yuka Onions?
Akane I remember writing about it somewhere, and I remember sticking it in myself.
Yuuka You wrote "onion" yourself?
Akane There was a time when I wondered why I wrote "onion.
Yuuka There was a year.
Yuuka I see.
Yuka: So, it's the first year.
Akane The first year. How about me?
Yuka Oh, no! Not even one?
Akane Not even one.
Yuka Not even one.
Akane What?
Akane Oh, you're right, it's right.
Yuka, properly.
Akane, I don't like that you're trying to look cool.
Yuuka Yes, like croissants.
Akane, it's funny that you even tell me what kind it is.
Yuuka, can you even tell me what kind it is?
Akane Then, I thought I should just write "croissant" and "melon bread" instead of "bread" and I'll do it now.
Yuuka It shows your personality, doesn't it?
Akane But you probably wanted to tell them that you like this one among fruits.
Akane I want to tell them by using parentheses.
Yuka For some reason, you are drawing a picture of Taipien with your right hand.
Akane Oh, an illustration.
Yuka Illustration.
Akane There was an illustration on the page.
Yuka You are drawing pictures.
Akane They asked us to submit pictures.
Akane That was probably in Kumamoto, so I knew I had Taipien in my mind.
Yuka Then this is the last one.
Akane Yes.
Yuka What have you grown in the past year?
Akane That's difficult.
Yuuka I wonder.
Akane Wow, what can I say?
Akane, let's start answering.
Akane, let's start.
Akane, your dance has grown.
Yuka: My performance has grown.
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
Oh!
I can take care of myself now.
A-ha-ha!
That's too heavy.
I think it's obvious now.
But I was in middle school back then.
I see.I see.
Oh, yeah.
From the very beginning.
I was the one to wake someone up.
Yeah, I did. Like, the first year or so.
I woke up the girl I was sharing a room with.
I woke them up all the time.
I was in charge of waking up the other people in the room.
So that's what it was like.
And you were away from your parents.
You were living in a hotel.
Maybe that's why you wrote that.
It's the first time I've been away from home for that long.
Like being away from home.
It was your first time, wasn't it?
That's true.
Mr. Takao, don't you have something?
Ah!
I could remember everyone's name.
Ha-ha-ha.
So cute!
You could remember 47 names?
No?
I'm still getting their names wrong at my age.
Ha-ha-ha.
Really.
We had to be from the same region.
Sometimes we didn't cross paths.
Really.
What did I write?
You hear that?
I'm learning to drink.
I'm learning to drink faster than before.
I think I'm getting a little talkier.
Oh, wow.
What an honor student
Yes, I'm sure.
Naru-tao
Oh no.
I was like this back then.
Yeah.
It came back to me a little
Just thinking about this answer
It was an emo time.
It was funny.
I laughed.
I found out that Shimoo has many charm points.
I see.
Ha-ha-ha.
Oh my God!
Anyway, it turns out I don't remember any of it.
That's true.
You do remember, don't you?
Yes, I remember a little bit.
I remember thinking...
Like how I was thinking at the time.
I vaguely remember.
That was amazing.
No, it was fun, this project.
I'm glad I did it.
I thought, "I'm glad I did it.
And I thought...
I'm happy!
I'll be happy this year!
I'm going to be happy this year!
It was a good time for me to look back and
I'm so happy!
Let's continue to do our best
Let's keep up the good work!
Let's not forget our first year's first thought.
I look forward to working with you again in the future.
Thank you very much.
That's all for now.
Bye bye!
Please look forward to the next video!